https://visionsespresso.com/terms-and-conditions-of-use-privacy-policy/

Victoria Arduino
Whip It!
1. Terms & Copyright
By accessing this website, you are agreeing to be bound by these website Terms and Conditions of Use, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site. The materials contained in this web site are protected by applicable copyright and trademark law.
The entire content included in this site, including but not limited to text, graphics or code is copyrighted as a collective work under the United States and other copyright laws, and is the property of Visions Espresso Service, Inc.. The collective work includes works that are licensed to Visions Espresso Service, Inc.. Copyright 2017, Visions Espresso Service, Inc., ALL RIGHTS RESERVED. Permission is granted to electronically copy and print hard copy portions of this site for the sole purpose of placing an order with Visions Espresso Service, Inc. or purchasing Visions Espresso Service, Inc. products. You may display and, subject to any expressly stated restrictions or limitations relating to specific material, download or print portions of the material from different areas of the site solely for your own non-commercial use, or to place an order with Visions Espresso Service, Inc. or to purchase Visions Espresso Service, Inc. products. Any other use, including but not limited to the reproduction, distribution, display or transmission of the content of this site is strictly prohibited, unless authorized by Visions Espresso Service, Inc.. You further agree not to change or delete any proprietary notices from materials downloaded from the site. This is the grant of a license, not a transfer of title, and under this license you may not:
modify or copy the materials;
use the materials for any commercial purpose, or for any public display (commercial or non-commercial);
attempt to decompile or reverse engineer any software contained on Visions Espresso Service Inc.'s website;
remove any copyright or other proprietary notations from the materials; or
transfer the materials to another person or "mirror" the materials on any other server.
This license shall automatically terminate if you violate any of these restrictions and may be terminated by Visions Espresso Service Inc. at any time. Upon terminating your viewing of these materials or upon the termination of this license, you must destroy any downloaded materials in your possession whether in electronic or printed format.
2. Trademark
All trademarks, service marks and trade names of Visions Espresso Service, Inc. used in this website are trademarks or registered trademarks of Visions Espresso Service, Inc..
3. Disclaimer
The materials on Visions Espresso Service, Inc.’s website are provided "as is". Visions Espresso Service, Inc. makes no warranties, expressed or implied, and hereby disclaims and negates all other warranties, including without limitation, implied warranties or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement of intellectual property or other violation of rights. Further, Visions Espresso Inc. does not warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or reliability of the use of the materials on its Internet web site or otherwise relating to such materials or on any sites linked to this site.
4. Limitations
In no event shall Visions Espresso Service Inc. or its suppliers be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, damages for loss of data or profit, or due to business interruption,) arising out of the use or inability to use the materials on Visions Espresso Service Inc.’s internet site, even if Visions Espresso Service Inc. or a Visions Espresso Service Inc. authorized representative has been notified orally or in writing of the possibility of such damage. Because some jurisdictions do not allow limitations on implied warranties, or limitations of liability for consequential or incidental damages, these limitations may not apply to you.
5. Revisions and Errata
The materials appearing on Visions Espresso Service Inc.’s web site could include technical, typographical, or photographic errors. Visions Espresso Service Inc. does not warrant that any of the materials on its web site are accurate, complete, or current. Visions Espresso Service Inc. may make changes to the materials contained on its web site at any time without notice. Visions Espresso Service Inc. does not, however, make any commitment to update the materials.
6. Links
Visions Espresso Service Inc. has not reviewed all of the sites linked to its internet web site and is not responsible for the contents of any such linked site. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by Visions Espresso Service Inc. of the site. Use of any such linked web site is at the user's own risk.
7. Site Terms of Use Modifications
Visions Espresso Service Inc. may revise these terms of use for its web site at any time without notice. By using this web site you are agreeing to be bound by the then current version of these Terms and Conditions of Use.
8. Governing Law
Any claim relating to Visions Espresso Service Inc.'s web site shall be governed by the laws of the State of Washington without regard to its conflict of law provisions. General Terms and Conditions applicable to Use of a Website.
9. Business Transfers
Should Visions Espresso Service, Inc., or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Visions Espresso Service, Inc. were to go out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets transferred to the acquiring party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Visions Espresso Service, Inc. may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.
10. Use of Site
Harassment in any manner or form on the website, including via e-mail, chat, or by use of obscene or abusive language, is strictly forbidden. Impersonation of others, including a Visions Espresso Service, Inc. or other licensed employee, host, or representative, as well as other members or visitors on the site is prohibited. You may not upload to, distribute, or otherwise publish through the site any content which is libelous, defamatory, obscene, threatening, invasive of privacy or publicity rights, abusive, illegal, or otherwise objectionable which may constitute or encourage a criminal offense, violate the rights of any party or which may otherwise give rise to liability or violate any law. You may not upload commercial content on the site or use the site to solicit others to join or become members of any other commercial online service or other organization.
Privacy Policy
At Visions Espresso Service Inc., we are committed to safeguarding and preserving the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document (the "Policy") has been provided for this purpose. This Policy explains what happens to any personal data that you provide to us, or that we collect from you whilst you visit our site and how we use cookies on this website. We do update this Policy from time to time so please do review this Policy regularly.
Information That We Collect
In running and maintaining our website we may collect and process the following data about you:
Information about your use of our site including details of your visits such as pages viewed and the resources that you access. Such information includes traffic data, location data and other communication data.
Information provided voluntarily by you. For example, when you register for information or make a purchase.
Information that you provide when you communicate with us by any means.
Use of Cookies
Cookies provide information regarding the computer used by a visitor. Visions Espresso Service, Inc. may use cookies where appropriate to gather information about your computer in order to assist us in improving our website.
Visions Espresso Service, Inc. may gather information about your general internet use by using the cookie. Where used, these cookies are downloaded to your computer and stored on the computer’s hard drive. Such information will not identify you personally; it is statistical data which does not identify any personal details whatsoever.
As you browse our website and other websites, online ad networks we work with may place anonymous cookies on your computer, and use similar technologies, in order to understand your interests based on your (anonymous) online activities, and thus to tailor more relevant ads to you.   If you do not wish to receive such tailored advertising, you can visit this page to opt out of most companies that engage in such advertising. (This will not prevent you from seeing ads; the ads simply will not be delivered through these targeting methods.)
Our advertisers may also use cookies, over which we have no control. Such cookies (if used) would be downloaded once you click on advertisements on our website.
You can adjust the settings on your computer to decline any cookies if you wish. This can be done within the “settings” section of your computer. For more information please read the advice at AboutCookies.org. To opt out of use of cookies please visit http://www.addthis.com/privacy/opt-out.
Use of Your Information
We use the information that we collect from you to provide our services to you. In addition to this we may use the information for one or more of the following purposes:
To provide information to you that you request from us relating to our products or services.
To provide information to you relating to other products that may be of interest to you. Such additional information will only be provided where you have consented to receive such information.
To inform you of any changes to our website, services or goods and products.
If you have previously purchased goods or services from us we may provide to you details of similar goods or services, or other goods and services, that you may be interested in.
Visions Espresso Service, Inc. never give your details to third parties to use your data to enable them to provide you with information regarding unrelated goods or services.
Storing Your Personal Data
By providing your personal data to Visions Espresso Service, Inc., you agree to this transfer, storing and processing of that data. We do our best to ensure that all reasonable steps are taken to make sure that your data is stored securely.
Unfortunately the sending of information via the internet is not totally secure and on occasion such information can be intercepted. Visions cannot guarantee the security of data that you choose to send us electronically, sending such information is entirely at your own risk.
Disclosing Your Information
Visions Espresso Service, Inc. will not disclose your personal information to any other party other than in accordance with this Privacy Policy and in the circumstances detailed below:
In the event that we sell any or all of our business to the buyer.
Where we are legally required by law to disclose your personal information.
To further fraud protection and reduce the risk of fraud.
Contacting Us
Please feel free to contact us regarding any matter relating to this Privacy Policy via email at info@visionsespresso.com or call 1-800-277-7277.
×
OK
